Mss.Rec.67 Mss.Rec.67
American Philosophical Society
Pawnee texts
1966
Mss.Rec.67
American Philosophical Society
1.0 Reel(s)
11 unindentified texts given in Pawnee only, nine in the South Band dialect, two in the Skiri dialect. Recorded in Pawnee, Oklahoma, in 1966.
1 sound tape reel (4 hr., 56 min.): analog, 3 3/4 ips, 2 track, mono; 7 in.
Allen, Sam
Cummings, Harry
Jim, Phillip
Parks, Douglas R.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Douglas Parks. This material was recorded with the assistance of a Phillips Fund grant.
Related Archival Materials
Project report with summary of work completed available in Phillips Fund collection (Mss.497.3.Am4).
Pawnee Indians; Pawnee language; Pawnee language--Texts; Sound recordings
- Audio recordings
  - Pawnee Text #1, 1966; 01-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:25:50; Cummings, Harry; Parks, Douglas R. (Douglas Richard), 1942-
    Scope and Contents note
    Unidentified text given in Pawnee only, South Band dialect. Contains occasional digital sound errors due to degradation on RDAT transfer tape.
    Existence and Location of Originals note
    This file is a compressed, digitized version of the original. The APS Library maintains the original format (Sound tape reel) as well as an uncompressed digitized version of this recording.
    Pawnee (Okla.); Pawnee language--Texts
  - Pawnee Text #2 and #3, 1966; 01-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:51:50; Cummings, Harry; Parks, Douglas R. (Douglas Richard), 1942-
    Unidentified text given in Pawnee only, South Band dialect. The break between texts 2 and 3 is unclear on the original recording, but may occur at 40:43, 41:09, or 42:44. Contains a small number of digital sound errors due to degradation on RDAT transfer tape.
  - Pawnee Text #4, 1966; 01-03; 1.0 .mp3; 00:13:51; Cummings, Harry; Parks, Douglas R. (Douglas Richard), 1942-
    Unidentified text given in Pawnee only, South Band dialect.
  - Pawnee Text #5, 1966; 01-04; 1.0 .mp3; 00:21:05; Cummings, Harry; Parks, Douglas R. (Douglas Richard), 1942-
  - Pawnee Text #6, 1966; 01-05; 1.0 .mp3; 01:17:45; Cummings, Harry; Parks, Douglas R. (Douglas Richard), 1942-
  - Pawnee Text #7, 1966; 01-06; 1.0 .mp3; 00:13:49; Cummings, Harry; Parks, Douglas R. (Douglas Richard), 1942-
  - Pawnee Text #8, 1966; 01-07; 1.0 .mp3; 00:11:30; Cummings, Harry; Parks, Douglas R. (Douglas Richard), 1942-
  - Pawnee Text #9, 1966; 01-08; 1.0 .mp3; 00:21:11; Allen, Sam; Parks, Douglas R. (Douglas Richard), 1942-
    Unidentified text given in Pawnee only, Skiri dialect.
  - Pawnee Text #10, 1966; 01-09; 1.0 .mp3; 00:16:52; Allen, Sam; Parks, Douglas R. (Douglas Richard), 1942-
  - Pawnee Text #11, 1966; 01-10; 1.0 .mp3; 00:42:22; Jim, Phillip; Parks, Douglas R. (Douglas Richard), 1942-